Now the story of a wealthy family
who lost everything...
and the one son
who had no choice...
but to keep them all together.
It's Arrested Development.
It was Monday morning...
and Michael Bluth
was nervous about meeting...
with the new prosecutor
ofhis father's criminal case.
I don't know what you're
so nervous about, Michael.
It's a new prosecutor.
It's a whole new beginning...
a new day, a new case,
a whole new set of lies.
- I'm not lying anymore, Mom.
- Michael was lying.
He found his fugitive father
earlier in the week...
and he was hiding him
in the attic...
where George Sr. Was currently
waiting for his breakfast.
About the business,
just for the record...
I was not involved with Dad
building houses in Iraq.
- That's exactly what I'm gonna tell them.
- Is that for Lindsay?
Because she's not scared
to eat in front of me anymore.
Those are
the whites only, yes?
These aren't for Lindsay.
These are mine.
Anyway, I'm not lying
anymore either, Michael.
I'm being lied...
on.
Wow. Now more's gonna
come up than go down.
I gotta get outta here.
- Hmm?
- I can't take this anymore.
I mean, she's just
so loving and affectionate.
L- l-This is not the woman
I fell in love with.
Oscar, please. You can't go.
You gotta stay, okay?
This is the nicest she's been since
she found out Rosa could breast-feed Buster.
Oh, Buster. Don't even bring that up.
He's well into his army training.
Actually, Buster had
hit a wall in his army training.
I can't do it! I can't make my bed,
and I can't do this either!
Aren't you supposed to yell at me and call me
"homo" and motivate me over this wall?
We can't do that anymore. Lawsuit.
In fact, it was a recent ruling...
prosecuted by the same man
who Michael was soon to meet with.
It's going to be a long time
before Sergeant Wendell Baker...
calls someone
"Private Homo" again.
God willing,
he'll fail boot camp.
Well, why wouldn't he?
He already failed day camp.
- Hey.
- Hi. Hey, Dad.
- You ready for the prosecutor?
- Hi. I hope so.
- How'd that math test work out?
- Oh, it was okay, I guess.
But- I don't know.
It was weird. I studied with Ann...
but I still got a B-minus.
- Ann got you a B-minus?
- Well, it wasn't Ann. She's an expert in math.
- Isn't that cute?
- Is it?
Michael felt his son
was setting the bar too low...
with his dating standards.
No, it wasn't Ann's fault. I think I just
ended up thinkin' about the questions too long.
And so, by the time I put
an answer down, I went with, like...
my fifth choice
or somethin' like that.
George Michael,
never settle for fifth choice.
Something better is gonna come along.
She just has to.
I think maybe sitting in the back
of the class with Ann is a bad idea.
You know,
she's just so pretty.
- I get distracted, I guess.
- Do you?
- I wish I could draw her nose.
- Maybe it's your eyes.
Maybe you need glasses...
for your grades.
Didn't you say you had
a hard time readin' the board...
- sittin' in the back row?
- No, I said I was in the back of the classroom.
- That's what I mean. Yeah?
- It's different. No. No.
Well, I don't know. Maybe.
- No, definitely. I'll call the eye doctor.
- I guess.
I'm gonna set you up
an appointment. Okay?
- Hey, gang.
- Tobias.
Oh. Ooh, I'm afraid I'll have to
take them to go. I'm late for the gym.
Oh, and also,
here's a number...
in case the Blue Man Group
calls and needs an understudy.
I just found out
that my cellular telephone was a lemon.
- It didn't work.
- Neither do you.
Pretty brave card for you to play.
I just can't stand it. Tobias getting in shape...
For a bunch
of slutty gym rats.
- What's wrong with your voice?
- Nothing. I've been going out.
Lindsay had been frequenting singles clubs...
also still hoping to make
her open marriage work-
- Whoo!
- which it won't.
- I didn't catch that.
- Whoo!
I wonder how many women
he's slept with, if any.
Lindsay, it's not
a competition.
Of course it is, Michael.
That's why they call it scoring.
- Maybe in the '70s.
- That many? We've only
been doing this for a month.
Instead of competing with Tobias,
why don't you try spending...
- a little more time with your daughter?
- Why? Tobias doing that?
At that moment, Lindsay's daughter...
- was in the process of wooing her own man.
- Who is it?
- Steve Holt!
- Maeby had even started
ordering unnecessary items...
just to have more occasions
to see him.
Uh, you ordered a "Memories
ofThanksgiving" basket?
- Wow, that looks great.
- Maeby, who's your friend?
- Is this your sister?
- No.
But you just made my day.
Thank you for the basket.
See ya.
He thinks I'm cute.
He's 19. He's a senior
at my high school.
And had been for several years.
You know what?
I think I am gonna spend more time
with my daughter.
I can't promise you I won't tell
the prosecutor about that.
- Where you been?
- Are you wearing my
dead wife's maternity clothes?
Yeah. It's the only thing
I could find.
- Where are the eggs?
- Doctor says they're bad for the baby.
- So, you ready for this new prosecutor?
- I was until you came back.
You're not gonna
turn me in, are you?
Because I had no idea there were sanctions
against, uh, Iraq.
You know, th-they sent me over there.
They said, "Go build."
Uh- Uh, Do I look like
a criminal mastermind to you?
How do you get this ham open?
I can't- I can't get this ham open.
I'm not gonna turn you in. But you have put me
in a position where I'm gonna have to lie.
Why did you come back here
in the first place?
Oh, no reason. Your mother happens
to be shtupping my brother, that's all.
I'm only here to find out
if I have a shot with her.
If she's really in love with Oscar-
I don't know- to hell with her.
I'll just-
I'll just leave.
- I'll never come back.
- Great. She's really in love with him.
That's very funny.
I need you to find out, okay?
'Cause ever since
l- I heard about this-
I can't sleep.
I can't- I can't eat.
Oh. Look, it just peels off.
Isn't that clever?
Later that day,
George Michael was having his eye exam...
and finding it to be just as difficult
as his math exam.
- One or two?
- Two. No. No, one.
- Okay. Two or three?
- Three.
Uh, unless three is too much
of an improvement.
I'm sorry.
Is one- Is one in the mix still?
And Michael met
with the new prosecutor, WayneJarvis.
I'm sorry. I don't understand
how this is not a conflict of interest.
You almost represented us,
and now you're the prosecutor.
The Patriot Act. Read it.
L-I'm not even the president anymore.
My brother Gob is.
I spoke with Gob.
He appears to know nothing.
Yeah, that's not an act.
He twice tried to microwave...
a Ding Dong
while it was still in its foil.
- Twice.
- Twice?
- Two times.
- In fact, Gob had been grilled earlier.
- I don't know anything about the business!
- We're gonna get you, Bluth.
We'll give you a few minutes
to think about what you want to do.
He knows less than anyone
we have ever questioned.
Gob knew too little
to know that, however...
and his confidence
had never been more shaken.
Andjust when he thought he couldn't
handle another embarrassment-
You're free to go.
Things could get very messy for you, Michael,
unless you have something to bargain with...
like, say, a fugitive.
- I don't know where to find such a thing.
- Look harder.
- There might be something in it for you.
- Something to get me off?
If you could find
a certain someone.
Can I have a moment alone
with my client, please?
Did you follow any of that?
Yeah. He's hinting that
he's gonna grant me immunity...
but only on the condition
that I turn in my father.
You know where your father is?
No, wait. Don't tell me now.
Okay. If you know,
give me a high five.
Mm-mmm.
Michael hadjust found out...
that his legal problems might go away
ifhe turned in his father.
It's just you and me now, huh?
No, Barry, l- I know
where my father is, okay?
He came back to make sure that my mother
wasn't really in love with my uncle.
He wants to know if he's still got a shot with her.
If he doesn't, he's leaving.
If he's got a shot with her,
just give me a little tap on the fanny.
- That's not gonna happen.
- Okay.
Then look, just tell him anything
he wants to hear to keep him from running.
We just have to keep him here
until we can hear...
what kind of deal
they're offering you.
You just trust me.
I'm a lot more competent than you can imagine.
Oh, I forgot to take
the tinfoil off too.
I really wanted that.
Buster, meanwhile, was sharing his failure...
with someone who was
well-versed on the subject.
I mean, I couldn't get over the wall.
They put me on suspension until I can.
Perhaps you need to find somebody
who can motivate you.
- Yeah, but who?
- And then it hit him.
Gob had always proven
a good motivator for Buster.
Do it!
When you do this without getting punched
in the chest, you'll have more fun.
- Thanks, Brother.
- Hey, Brother...
how would you like to go
to the old playground with me?
I'm sure as hell not gonna go back to work.
I'm never going back there.
Oh. Well, then perchance I might be able
to borrow your cellular telephone?
I'm not fit
to run a company.
And I don't deserve
a fancy phone.
Well, the Blue Man Group might need me.
And I do deserve a fancy phone.
They didn't, and he doesn't.
Michael knew he couldn't
let his father get away.
So he decided to see ifhis mother
and Oscar really were in love.
So, come on. Aren't you really just dating
Oscar to get back at Dad?
Oh, it may have
started as that...
but I have
fallen in love with Oscar.
And it's so nice not to have to worry
about getting pregnant.
The doctor said
I couldn't be a mother now if I tried.
And that was without
even interviewing me.
Here you go. Hot tea.
Because that's what you are-
a hottie.
Stop me from pouring this on myself.
I can't take this anymore.
All right. Now, listen, Oscar.
Maybe you should think
about moving on, you know.
This really isn't your scene,
with the sweaters and the furniture.
Maybe you should take a leap at freedom,
like my father.
Just run.
Is that her rape horn?
It's more like
a starter's pistol.
Run.
Meanwhile, Tobias set about
learning how to operate his new cell phone.
Oh!
And Lindsay tried to spend
more time getting to know her daughter.
Hi, baby. Oh, Steve. Hi.
- Hi.
- What are you doing here?
I thought I'd spend a little time
with my daughter.
After all, it hasn't been that long
since I've been in high school.
Is that a fire?
- We have to go to class.
- Okay. Well, this was fun.
Maybe later we can all spend a little
more time together. Go shopping. Get a drink.
I'm in school.
And I'm 15.
Oh. Well, I'm much, much, much...
older than 15.
- You don't look it.
- Oh, Steve.
He thinks I'm young.
You made my day again!
- Your mom's pretty, uh, out there.
- She's not my mom.
But she said
you were her daughter.
His daughter.
That's my dad.
- That's a dude?
- And the worst part is...
he thinks he's passing.
Right outside the school,
Buster tried to put his own plan...
into action
by stirring up old memories.
What do you say?
I need your help to get over the wall. Push me.
I'm the pathetic one, Buster,
not you.
I totally freaked out in front
of that prosecutor today.
Like a little girl
in a little dress-
little saddle shoes,
little pigtails.
Wow, that does sound
like a little girl.
Come on, get my ire up.
Push me!
Oh.
Oh, this is turning out to be
much more fun than I'd hoped.
It was fun. But it wasn't
making him a better soldier.
Push me higher.
Ooh! I'll do it.
Whoo!
And Michael reported to
his father about his meeting with the prosecutor.
- Prosecutor offer you a deal?
- That was not said.
But, uh, more importantly, you should know
that it seems like Oscar's on his way out.
- Really?
- Yeah. So just sit tight,
and everything should be fine.
Wow. Hey, by the way,
I broke this thing. L-
- What the hell is it anyway?
- That's a breast pump, Dad.
Oh. Well, I did not
use it for that.
And so Michael went to meet the prosecutor.
I felt obligated to share
some photographs with you.
I obtained these from
the Bluth Company e-mail server.
You tapped into our e-mail?
That's legal?
I'm going for a hot Ding Dong.
Hot Ding Dong? Yeah?
Michael, this is a close-up satellite photograph
of the Iraqi countryside.
See this little series of hills
around that stream?
Those are bunkers.
We believe that those bunkers...
contain weapons
of mass destruction.
We also think that your father
was building on that land to hide them.
Which is why that photograph
was on his e-mail.
- Are you serious?
- Almost always.
I was once called the worst audience
participant Cirque Du Soleil ever had.
- This is a big accusation.
- I did not find their buffoonery amusing.
- About my father.
- He's guilty, Michael, of medium to heavy treason.
That proves it.
You can't protect him.
Turn him in
and immunity is yours.
Michael returned home
to confront his father.
- Michael?
Mom was just here
looking for you.
She's claiming Oscar's disappeared
because of something you said.
- Can't talk right now.
- Really?
What's wrong with your voice?
I can talk, sure.
I didn't say anything to Oscar.
- Anything else?
- No.
Oh. Hey, did I tell you?
I accidentally ran into Steve Holt.
Wow. Everything about you
is so womanly.
You're everything
a woman should be.
Thank you, Steve.
We ended up
making a lunch date.
I thought you were
spending time with Maeby.
Yeah. I'll have to
reschedule her.
But Mom isn't the only one "finding love"
where she least expects it. Her words.
Wh-Whoa! Finding love-
She said that? Where, here?
Yeah, she won't
shut up about him.
She said "tingling,"
like, 75 times.
Gets me tingling.
And, you know, with Oscar there's tingling.
- She said those words in this house?
- Yeah.
Dad?
Hello?
Michael hadjust discovered
that his father had escaped from the attic.
Hello?
This is gonna sound like a strange question,
but have you seen Dad?
Of course not.
And I'm not talking to you.
You tried to scare away Oscar,
which didn't work.
- He's back.
- I just, uh-
I just wanted to have sex with you.
That's-That's all I'm good for.
Did you hear that?
He said he just wants to-
- Good-bye, Mom.
- Have sex with me.
- You smell like a pinecone.
- Yeah, that's the weed.
I went to my, uh,
my- hole trailer...
and l- I smoked some
like a cigarette.
Should we take it
into the bedroom?
- Only if you really love me.
- Of course I do.
Ohh.
What's wrong with you?
Where are you going?
I'm on mushrooms!
I'm on bad mushrooms!
And soon,
the prosecutor's evidence became public.
We've obtained photographs that officials
call definite proof of W.M.D.'s in Iraq.
What that means
for your weekend at 10:00.
It seems that due
to the new information-sharing provisions...
in the Patriot Act, the photos
had made the rounds...
through several branches
of government...
and ultimately
to the U.S. Army itself.
I just came back to tell you.
I can't do that wall.
There's no time for that.
We're shipping out without you.
- What?
- Didn't you see?
- Pick it up. Pick it up.
- Weapons of mass destruction?
- Those bastards.
- I did not say that.
Are you gonna let that slide?
Are you gonna allow your children...
and your children's children...
and any children
that I might have out there...
to live in fear
for the rest of their lives?
Climb that wall, homo!
Climb it.
Andjust as the men
thought the day could get no more surprising...
it did.
Ohh! Ooh!
When you do this without getting
punched, you'll have more fun.
- Oh, hey, George Michael.
- Oh, hi.
They found W.M.D.'s in Iraq,
so we got a half-day.
Cool. So I got
a "C" on my math test.
Not anticipating
a good reaction on that.
Well, the "B" got you glasses.
Maybe this time you'll get a neck brace.
Anyways, have you seen my mom?
Seems possible.
- She's on her way to meet Steve Holt.
- I thought you liked him.
I do. I'm crazy about him.
But he's obsessed with her.
That's all he wants
to talk about.
Lindsay felt bad.
Perhaps she had hurt her daughter...
by putting herself first.
But she would have felt worse
if she'd remained even a moment longer.
But it's only because
he thinks she's got a penis.
Oh, I told him
she was a tranny.
Meanwhile, Michael was still up in the attic.
Dad, what's goin' on?
Somebody could see you.
What's the difference, Mike?
You're turning me in, aren't you?
They say you're involved in something
real big, Dad. They've got photos.
Not true. But go.
Knock yourself out. Turn me in.
I went and I saw for myself.
She's in love with him.
Then why did you come back?
Why didn't you just leave forever like you said?
And go where?
Make a deal for yourself, Mike.
I got no love
in my life anymore.
And Michael realized for the first time...
that his father was capable
ofhaving his heart broken.
Later that day,
Michael had his meeting with the prosecutor.
So, where the hell is he?
Come on, Bluth. What's it gonna be?
Your father or your freedom?
And Michael had to do the right thing.
I don't know
what happened to him.
Michael, when we started talking to you,
we didn't have anything.
But now... we got something.
- And you're gonna do time for it.
- Those are the pictures?
They're all over the news.
- Those are balls.
- What?
Barry was right. Tobias had
inadvertently photographed himself...
while learning to use
his camera phone.
See, uh, this close,
they always look like landscape.
Nope, you're lookin' at balls.
Soon, forensic scientists confirmed this.
And for the second time
in two days...
the information-sharing network
put into place by the Patriot Act...
was put to use.
They're balls?
We're looking at balls. Let's turn it around.
Copy on balls. We're turning.
And eventually, the news
traveled back to the source.
We got one wrong,
and we do apologize.
I'm on TV.
And Michael returned home a free man.
You got the glasses.
Now you'll do better on those math exams.
I think I blew the eye exam too.
Every time I take these off, I feel better.
Let me see 'em.
- I've seen this before.
- For a while, George Michael...
had shared a room
with his Uncle Tobias.
- Oh, th-there's a ladder.
- I don't need it.
Yeah, I don't think
you need glasses, Son.
Well, if the cops are waiting,
I'm ready to go.
I got nothin'
since your mother deserted me.
You know,
you-you deserted her, Dad.
You know, you escaped,
and then you faked your death.
I'm not so sure she sees you
as that reliable.
But, listen,
for what it's worth...
I did not turn you in.
- You didn't?
- No.
And I don't know whether
it's just Tracy's maternity clothes...
but it's very nice to see
a softer side of you.
Although I'm sorry that you feel
you have no love in your life.
Well, I don't-
I don't feel that way anymore.
Thanks.
Been a long time
since someone stood up for me.
- Found her perfume, huh?
- Just a little left in the bottle.
- Well, that was the end of it.
- Yeah.
- It's nice on you.
- Thank you.
On the next
Arrested Development.
Oscar returns to find
a now-distant Lucille.
I'm back.
But just for now.
'Cause you get
on my case- shoo-
- I am out of here.
- Then go. Who needs you?
Which was what attracted him to her...
- in the first place.
- God, I missed you.
- Lindsay reconciles with her daughter.
- Hey, Mom. I got you somethin'.
That is so sweet.
You know what? I was hoping
we could go to dinner tonight.
Oh, I thought you were gonna
go see Steve Holt at school.
No, I just wanted
to check him out...
and make sure he's good enough
for my daughter.
- Is it-
- It's a "Sheh-ma-lee."
It's gorgeous.
I'm wearing it to dinner.
Tobias, traumatized by the public exposure...
returns to
an unfortunate quirk.
Thank God!
My cutoffs.
There were
cutoffs up here?