Now the story of a wealthy family
who lost everything...
and the one son
who had no choice...
but to keep them all together.
It's Arrested Development.
Michael Bluth
hadjust been stunned to discover...
that a contract his company was
counting on was being cut back.
You initially told us to design and build
22 homes. Now you're saying 18.
That doesn't give us enough
capital to complete the job.
And we've already got the blueprints
drawn up and everything.
Well, that part wasn't true.
But they would've.
That was a very important phone call.
I don't have much time, Michael. Tobias is
about to walk in here any minute asking for a job.
I need you to hire him.
- Hi. I'm sor-
- Look, it isn't my idea, it's his.
But I need a break
from Mrs. Featherbottom.
Since moving out, Tobias had
been pretending to be a British housekeeper...
as a way to be close to his family.
However, his desire to now be discovered
as himself was becoming bothersome.
Can't you just tell him you know
that he's Mrs. Featherbottom?
No. She's the only one
who can hand wash my delicates.
Yeah, the real Tobias
wouldn't do that.
- Wouldn't do what?
- Be Michael's assistant.
Well, that's what I came
down here to ask about.
I think you'll find me
more than qualified.
It's really not that simple.
Uh, you'd have to submit a résumé.
Booyah!
- Wow. Gobias Industries.
- Gobias.
- Right. I remember, yeah.
- As in "Go buy us a cup of-"
It looks like you might be
a little too qualified.
Hang on. Why don't you let your new
assistant take all this down?
Wow, you are gung ho.
You're getting a new assistant?
Is this because the order was cut back?
No. But if you are concerned
about keeping your job...
focus on keeping
unwanted visitors out of my office.
I have rabies, Michael. You know that.
Today was day four of my shots.
Starla had been bitten by...
a well-known music producer's guard dog.
Michael, Starla told us
about the cutback.
You know, a lot of our overhead
is tied up in the fact...
we are on the top floor
of a very expensive building.
- If we move just one floor lower-
- Ted, everything's fine.
I got it all under control,
and nobody needs to move.
- I'm sorry. Ted, is it?
- Yes.
Ted. Did Ted make an appointment?
- No, I just work down the hall and-
- No.
Well, then, Ted can get
the hell out of this office!
- I'm talking-
- You get the hell out!
- And that's how you keep out unwanted visitors.
- Thank you.
Although, if I may, let me
take off my assistant skirt...
and put on my Barbra Streisand in The Prince
of Tides ass-masking therapist pantsuit.
- What?
- The reason that you can't accept my help...
is the same reason you can't
hear that gentleman's idea-
because you have to be in
total control of everything.
And it's going to make
you sick if you can't let go.
- Hey, I'm fine.
- Oh?
Oh! Ooh!
- See? He's right.
You've got a control problem.
But I know this Eastern medicine store,
Ancient Chinese Secret.
Ancient Chinese Secret, huh?
- I sent Gob there for his migraines.
- It's just a cramp. I'm fine.
In fact, Gob was at Ancient
Chinese Secret at that moment...
- but not for a migraine.
- Yeah, I need a tea to give my dingle less tingle.
Me quick, want slow.
Wait, that's Indian.
Tea for dong.
- Sweet blade.
- It's the Sword of Destiny. It's full of ancient magic.
Oh, yeah?
You into magic?
Still, where'd the lighter fluid come from?
- So, is it for sale? I could use it in my act.
- Maybe.
Sword of Destiny hundreds of years old.
Come with ancient story
of warning and-
Yeah, I make up my own patter.
Just ring it up with the dong tea.
And Gob caught up with Michael.
- Michael. Been lookin' for you.
- Looks like you're looking for dragons,
in the future.
I wouldn't mock
the Sword of Destiny, Michael.
Careful with that, Gob.
- Bleeding?
- Nope.
Yeah, that's blood.
It'll get better before the show.
That's what I need you for, Michael.
I can't perform my illusion
at the Gothic Castle...
because I've been banned
from the Magicians' Alliance.
I need you to register as the magician,
and I'm the lowly assistant.
Then we get on the stage,
and you ram the Sword of Destiny into my belly.
- What do you think?
- Really picked up steam there
at the end, but I can't.
I've gotta teach George Michael how to drive.
And then I gotta get right back here, because-
Michael, if I make this comeback...
I'll buy you 100 George Michaels
you can teach to drive!
- You're losing blood, aren't you?
- Probably. My socks are wet.
Sorry.
You'll be sorry!
Wait, that doesn't work after his line.
And Michael rushed home
to teach his son to drive.
Knock, knock. Hey, Maeby.
George Michael, ready to drive?
- I don't have much time.
- Get me behind that wheel.
Oh, no, you will
not be behind the wheel.
You'll observe me while
I demonstrate some things, okay?
I'll be quizzing you too, hotshot.
I'm gonna go grab the video camera.
- And then, school's in.
- I'd skip.
Well, no, I need to learn.
You can't get around
anywhere without a driver's license.
Actually, Maeby had received
a company car from the movie studio...
where she was secretly
posing as an executive.
But currently, George Sr.
Was in the attic making a videotape-
- This is my demand.
- when Michael found him.
What's the deal with the turban?
Huh?
Pretty smart, huh?
- And-And it's warm too.
- Guess that makes sense.
Oh, hey, I heard about that reduced order.
Those bastards.
This videotape is for our employees.
You take this and play it. This will
reassure them that someone is in charge.
Well, someone is in charge, Dad.
I'm in charge. I've never even taken a sick day.
No, a real authority.
My presence needs to be, uh, reinstated.
His first effort at doing so
had already failed.
When do you start
being my mole at my company?
Actually, Michael turned me
down for the job.
- What?
- Something to do with their
housing order being cut back.
Oh, my God, that's a horrible sign-
Ow! Damn it!
I'm the authority,
so I will save the company.
And I say no videotape. Ooh!
- You oughta take a sick day. Get out of that office.
- Don't count on it, Dad.
And Michael was finally ready
to make his son watch him drive.
All right, stair car basics. In order to
get this thing up to a minimum speed...
you gotta jam on the gas pedal
for about a minute, okay?
But in order to slow this thing down...
you gotta get immediately
back on the brake pedal...
'cause you got about
two tons of stairs behind you.
We're gonna cover the hydraulic flaps
and the riser system...
after I tell you the basics
about how to avoid a hop-on.
But the first thing
we're gonna go over- Ow!
And that's when Michael decided
that perhaps it was time for a sick day.
Let's go over the route
to the hospital. Ow!
My baby is sick,
but Mother is here to nurse you.
- Well, now I'm a little sicker.
- Well, don't you worry about work today.
I am ready and willing
to step up and take over.
Yeah, and I'll get George Michael
ready for his driving test.
I'm gonna teach him when I get out. And no
one's taking over for me at the Bluth Company.
Michael, this is what we talked about.
I'm sure they'll do just fine without you.
Well, you're wrong,
because we're in crisis there.
They need to know that
I'm in charge and I'm in con-
I'm peeing.
Am I peeing?
I'm sorry. We gave you a little
something to relax you.
It may have taken the tingle out
of your genitals.
Oh, no. You're not
taking care of my son.
I'm sorry to say this, but it's too late
for me to do anything for your son.
Let him keep talking.
Because Dr. Stein here has already
been assigned to his case.
- You're lucky. He's the best.
- Well, only in the county.
But I'm certainly good enough to
take out that appendix of yours.
- Appendix?
- I don't buy it. Could be a hernia.
Or it could be your colon.
I'd want to get in there
and find some answers.
Well, I am the best doctor
in the state.
But if you don't trust my decisions-
No, no, no. No. You're the doctor.
You see, he's the authority here.
We need to respect him just like the employees
at the Bluth Company need to respect me.
Okay, I'm going to put you on this machine
to slow down your heart rate.
Hopefully not too slow, because
it's already dangerously slow as it is.
Whatever you think, Doctor.
Meanwhile, Gob was still trying
to arrange his comeback in magic.
So I'd be a magician
and you'd be my assistant?
Well, on paper, yes.
But once the show starts,
and you ram that sword through my belly...
people will know that I'm the one
who belongs back in the Alliance.
The kind of trick that I can put on a DVD,
like Tony Wonder does.
Tony Wonder had startled the
world by baking himself into a loaf ofbread.
He sold the DVD's of it on his Web site...
which many claimed suffered
due to its pop-up ads.
- Thanks.
I'm finally being treated like a real person,
not some deformed-
Hook! Forgot about
that thing, Elephant Man.
Gonna have to figure out something to do
so that people can look at you...
without wanting to kill themselves.
That night, George Sr.
Heard about Michael's illness.
The employees are gonna panic.
They need to know that someone's in control.
- And how do we do that?
- Booyah!
And at the Gothic Castle...
- Buster had been outfitted with
a mechanical Halloween hand.
- Whoa!
Looks like you've got some dirty ears.
Well, you're not on the banned list,
so you can go on at 6:00.
6:00? Looks like you'll be my opener.
Tony Wonder!
You like bread?
- Yeah.
- Have some.
- Wow, it's warm.
- How did you do that?
Oh, ho, ho.
Magicians only.
I folded it up into some squares,
and I put it in a pouch under my shirt...
and then I pull it out, and I make it
look like it came out of my skin.
- Wow, that sounds easy.
- Keep it to yourself.
And good luck up there tonight.
And you! You'll get there someday.
I started out as a little "W."
Somehow I became a big one.
I don't even know how
it happened. All right?
My eye!
Enjoy the Hanukkah cookie, man.
What a cool guy.
- Tobias had been sent to the office by George Sr.
- My name is Dr. Tobias Fünke...
and I'll be filling in for Michael,
who is not sick.
In fact, just today I saw
a sliver of his buttocks...
and they're as fresh and firm
as a Georgia peach, so not to worry.
But before you all rise up and say,
"Well, let's make this man our leader,"
well, I think that won't be
necessary after you see this.
Is this right?
Meanwhile, Lindsay had
also violated Michael's authority...
and was teaching
George Michael to drive.
Sure you don't want me
to watch you for a while?
Driving is about confidence, George Michael.
Jam on it! It feels great, right?
Now, put your foot on the brake.
There's a light in a half mile.
Meanwhile,
Buster and Gob had begun...
the Sword of Destiny illusion
at the Gothic Castle.
Ah-ah, ah-ah, ah-ah! Ooh! Whoo!
Stop it, Buster.
- And now our magic trick.
- Illusion.
Silence, slave!
In this magic trick,
I'm going to put a sword...
- through my assistant's tummy.
- No patter.
May I have the trick sword, please?
It's a real sword, master.
Oh-ho!
- Ooh! Hoo, hoo, hoo!
- We've got 'em. I'm gonna milk this for a minute.
Okay.
My hand! My hand!
And the audience wasn't
the only one impressed by the performance.
Bravo. Hey, give us a sec,
would you, Candida?
My brother's widow.
It's- up.
Hey, so the accident angle.
Right on.
- Oh, thank you, very much.
- No, thank you.
The "How'd he do dats?" ate it up.
Sorry. That's what we call the audience.
No, l-I know- I know about all that.
Used to have a solo act.
There was talk of boiling me
into a bisque at one point.
Not registering. But you hitched
your wagon to the right star.
- I want you guys on my next DVD.
- You want us for Use Your Illusion?
Actually, some band has
got the rights to that title.
So, I'm thinkin', like,
Use Your Illusion II.
But, yeah, meet me out there tomorrow.
And, uh, if you get thirsty-
Have a free round of drinks,
courtesy ofTony Wonder.
- It's a Subway Sub Club card.
- That's a magician.
Oh, it still needs three stamps.
Michael hadjust come
around from his appendectomy.
Give me the phone. I want to call
George Michael, tell him I'm okay.
He's on his way here.
We passed him on the road.
He was doing really well.
Had his first hop-on.
What are you talking about?
He's driving? I told Lindsay not to teach him.
- I was going to videotape that hop-on.
- Hey, Dad. How're you feeling?
Bad, George Michael. I just found out
Lindsay's teaching you how to drive.
Yeah. She's still trying to get the stairs
unwedged from the emergency room overhang.
I was gonna teach you. Just forget
everything she told you, and we'll start over.
Oh, for God's sake.
Tobias is right.
- What?
- You have to control everyone's life.
I don't know where you get that from.
Oscar, stop licking that sore.
- I'm not.
- Well, the operation went pretty smoothly.
But once I got in there,
the appendix wasn't so inflamed. D'oh.
- I knew it.
- Okay. Well, can we get me out of here?
I gotta retrain my son how to drive,
and I need to stop by the office...
- to make sure my business doesn't go to hell.
- And, not so fast, Michael.
There seems to be a bacterial infection
from the operation...
- which left an abscess in your abdominal wall.
- Ew.
I know, it's pretty gross.
It could heal on its own.
But I say we go in there
Dr. Stein-style and cut it out.
I want to show these interns what
the best doctor in Southern California can do.
- Well, I respect your decision.
- I'll check on you soon.
Michael, this crazy point you're trying to
make about respecting authority is absurd.
And one day, you're gonna wake up and find
out it has caused you nothing but trouble.
- And you are peeing again.
- And as the anesthesia took hold...
Michael realized he was going to
wake up to nothing but trouble.
The F.B.I. Has pinpointed the location
of escaped convict George Bluth today...
thanks to a tape turned in by a rabid
and disgruntled employee.
The F.B.I. Has matched the design of the attic
to one of Saddam Hussein's Iraqi houses.
- And it appears his son is with him.
- This is my demand.
Booyah!
Buster and Gob were
waiting to meet with Tony Wonder.
All right. He's gonna lowball us, so just
let me do the talking, all right, Busty?
This DVD is the destiny
the sword has chosen for me.
I wonder where he is.
Did somebody say, "Wonder"?
He just appeared out of nowhere,
in front of that dumbwaiter.
Actually, he'd been hiding inside
the dumbwaiter for over 20 minutes...
- waiting for someone to use the word "wonder."
- I wonder where he is.
Oh, hey, you've got a piece
of lettuce on your shoulder.
Ta-da!
Part of the trick.
So, let's get down to business, shall we?
Hey, can you, uh, go wait with
the other assistants over there?
- What?
- No, whatever you say to me, you can say to him.
I grant him magic sanctuary.
Uh, you grant me? Come on,
you can't just make up-
- That's fine.
I second the sanctuary.
But with a clause of silence.
So, I want you guys to be on Use Your Illusion.
Only now it's "Allusion" with an "A."
So if you guys want to put
an allusion in there somewhere...
like, you know, Poe or something or-
Don't do Poe, 'cause I'm doin' Poe.
- What about Chaucer?
- Just not Poe, okay?
And, uh, I don't think
we need, uh, your assistant.
- What?
- Eh! Clause of silence.
Look, my assistant is my partner.
I need him.
For what, Buster, huh?
You're the magic.
Check out those moves you're doin', man.
They're in their own orbit.
Look at Tiagra, my girl.
Don't look at her.
'Cause you look at her and it affects her
in a way that I don't feel comfortable with.
Or go for it. I don't care, whatever.
I'm just sayin' it's your world.
All right, you know what?
The trick is on you, Tony Wonder.
I'm the magician. He's the assistant.
We don't need him!
The real Sword of Destiny trick
hasn't even been performed yet. Ta-da!
Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa. Wait.
Are you tellin' me that you have a
multi-stage trick with hidden identities?
That's right. And I'm gonna perform
the real trick this afternoon.
- I guess we'll see what you can do then.
- I guess we will.
Ow! Darryl, I told you to move that-
chair 10 times!
And clean the-
Dumbwaiter while you're at it!
Oh, I was really hoping
for a graham cracker.
That would have been
a good spot for a trick.
- Michael awoke from his second surgery.
- Morning, sleepyhead.
- Did you get the abscess?
- Well, uh, we had a little whoopsie.
See, we got the abscess, but I think
we might have left some snippers in there.
It's not very likely, but one of the assistants
having taken them is even less likely.
- Unless I left them in my scrubs.
- Michael, good news.
They think George is in Iraq.
All the pressure's off him.
That was on the news?
I thought that I dreamt that.
- Oh, they're gonna think that I'm there. Ow!
- But not to worry.
Tobias said he's handling it
with the F.B. I...
and the employees have
everything under control.
No, that's the worst thing possible.
They think the company's in trouble
and that I'm in Iraq.
I gotta get down there.
I need your car keys.
And so Michael
and George Michael headed to the office.
- Right here, gentlemen.
- Which is how Tobias missed him.
Michael Bluth is not... in Iraq.
Michael, back to bed with you.
You look awful.
Michael rushed to the office
only to find that his worst fears had come true.
We're too late. It's gone.
Everybody said that I was too controlling...
but I walk away for one minute,
look what happens to the company.
I mean, this is why
I didn't want- Damn it!
Dad, you should probably take it easy.
I said that this would happen. I said respect
my authority, but no one would listen.
Everybody had
their own better id- Ow!
And maybe it was the stress
or even the misplaced snippers...
but Michael had never felt worse.
However, thanks to taking on his authority,
the employees had never felt better.
- Ted?
- Oh, hey, Michael. Good news.
We leased the top floor to another company
and moved down here.
But we can stay in business
without having to build the extra houses.
We did it.
We did it!
- You're goin' down, right?
- Whoo!
And back at the Gothic Castle,
Gob was performing his illusion.
Hey, after I cut the candle in half,
switch out the real sword for the fake one.
What are you doin'?
I'm Gob Bluth.
I'm the real magician.
This man is only the assistant.
Buster, the sword.
Handle first. Handle first.
Oh, my fingers!
He cut off my-
fingers!
- Oh!
- No!
- Guy is good. Damn good.
- Bravo!
I'm not kidding!
He cut off my- fingers!
- I didn't know we had taquitos.
- More! More!
And Michael came to a decision.
You know what, George Michael?
I think I'm going to give up
some of my authority, starting now.
You drive home. All right?
Unfortunately,
Michael's decision to let his son...
drive a car with a more
responsive gas pedal...
was not a good decision.
Your leg's gonna be fine, Michael.
And I wouldn't worry about
getting hit by any more cars.
I've shortened your calf muscles to
theoretically increase your jumping ability.
But if it works,
I could be the best in the world.
I want the other doctor back.
On the next Arrested Development.
- Michael gets a new roommate.
- Your fingers have been perfectly reattached.
Go ahead, take a look.
My middle finger
and index finger are-
Switched for the first time ever.
- Nice job, Frank.
- Amazing.
And the F.B.I. Finds footage more
troublesome than they'd originally thought.
It appears there was
something else on the videotape.
We think it's a terrorist training film.
You're not half the man he was!
This kid's got moves.