NARRATOR: George Michael was
playing a game of lie tag
- with his father.
- Wait, I bet we're sitting
in the exact same traffic.
God, I just hope there
are no kids on that plane.
500 bucks they find a dead kid...
Currently each claimed
to be stuck in traffic
behind a light aircraft
that had landed on the 605.
Loving that kid too much and
letting him fly the plane.
And... and you know what? One more thing.
I think I accidentally had
the phone flipped around.
I recorded my face the
whole time, you know?
Smartphone, stupid man.
Pal, why don't you loop
around and film this thing.
Someone's got to tell the story.
Michael hung up feeling confident
he'd had the last word.
- (phone chimes)
- Kidding me?
GEORGE MICHAEL: Missed you again, damn.
But, you know, I got out of my car here,
and I'm, uh, standing
here now with a paramedic
named Tim Ridge... Ridgley...
Can I record some video over there?
- No cameras allowed.
- No camera...
They're being real tight-assed
about this camera thing.
But George Michael was
proving more adept at lying
than anyone suspected.
Getting back in my car now.
You know, thank God we
weren't on that plane.
Which would come in handy with a woman
who only knew him as George Maharis.
- Hey.
Hey, sorry, that was my dad.
He can be kind of hard to
get off the phone sometimes.
(sighs) Tell me about it.
At least he wasn't drunk
and bitching about Don Ameche
not knowing his lines inCocoon.
He... he's actually great.
If anything, I've been
kind of a lousy son lately,
but, you know, it's just...
I mean, at some point,
I've got to start living my life.
No, I know. I mean, my dad is
the nicest guy in the world,
- but he just doesn't get it.
- (Elevator bell dings)
I have to live my life my way.
It's like he's always checking up on me.
- Does yours do that?
- Yeah, no, once in a while.
You want to go in here?
(gasps) Yeah, okay.
♪ ♪
- MICHAEL: Ron.
- RON: Hey.
No, no, it's Michael. Michael Bluth...
doing the film about my family and...
RON: Yeah, when are we gonna
get your kid's signature though?
- MICHAEL: I'm working on it.
- Oh.
- And I... I got a hold of him.
- Oh, oh.
And we're gonna meet here tonight,
but I think that he's blowing me off.
RON: Well, yeah, kids will be kids, right?
MICHAEL: Well, you know, a month ago,
I would've told you that he
and I were exactly the same,
that we were twins, you know?
But now, I wouldn't even think of
my son as my brother.
Although, in fairness,
this is something a Bluth brother would do.
Now the story of a family
whose future was abruptly cancelled
and the one son who had no choice
but to keep himself together.
It's George Michael's Arrested Development.
NARRATOR: George Michael was a new man.
He had finally cast off the shackles
- of his cautious persona,
- MAN: Come on, man, throw it.
And he was ready to play with the big boys.
- Okay, I'm good!
- You all right?
That's it for me.
You guys keep playing.
(laughs)
Oh, too funny.
- Oh!
- (Men cheering)
But later, at the student health center,
he was reminded of the man
who'd always supported him...
Who would you like us to
call in case of an emergency?
And who he'd now twice hurt.
My dad.
And that night, Michael,
trying to impress Rebel
by being a down-to-earth rich guy...
although by doing so, he was neither...
Beverly Hills billionaires
who can't go two minutes
- without putting his phone...
- Got this call.
I got to take this. Hold
on one second. Hello.
Hey, George Michael.
You stuck in traffic, pal?
You know, I just feel terrible
that we couldn't get together
the other night, and,
uh, I miss you, you know.
But I'm free all night if...
But Michael hadn't forgiven George Michael.
People in politics involved and I just...
You know, I can't get away this time.
It seemed the two men were
growing less alike every day.
And although George Michael felt guilty,
- George Maharis was already
- Oh, God, I've got to get this.
Planning his evening
with, as it turned out,
someone who had also just
been put off by his father.
Hi, Rebel, it's George Mi... haris.
My night just freed up, and I
was wondering if you wanted...
I thought you were having
dinner with your dad.
Well, you know older guys...
the night ends for them at 8:00.
I think I could use a
break from the old guys.
And I've already got
some birth control in me
that I paid for myself,
and I'd hate to let it go to waste.
Well, that's perfect,
because I'm not quite
ready to have children.
So, as he straightened up his room,
- he got this call.
- (Cell phone ringing)
- Hey, Dad.
- George Michael, hey.
Got out of it.
I just... I made a ton of people angry,
but you know what I always say: family...
Well, aw, gosh, you know, I
really wanted to, uh, do that,
but I just had this work thing come up.
And, uh, it's like you always say:
family first, unless there's a work thing,
and then work first.
I have said that, too.
- Uh, so another time.
- Okay.
But he had another problem
he had to deal with.
- P-Hound.
- Hey, George Michael.
- Hey.
- Look, I got us a peace pizza.
Oh, that's great... hey, you've got to go.
What did you do with my stuff?
- I've just got a girl coming over and...
- Maeby?
It's not Maeby, no. But,
um, could you please leave?
Okay, first you "F" me with Fakeblock,
and then you're gonna kick me out
when you have a hottie coming over?
- I have roommate rights.
- Well, you know what?
You voided your rights when you took
this picture of Maeby brushing her teeth.
- Not against the rules.
- Still a little weird,
- don't you think?
- But not against the rules.
- Well...
- You know what?
This is no longer a peace pizza.
- That is a war pizza.
- Okay, that's fine.
Do you want to take it back or... ?
No, I already ate. Th... that's for you.
- Oh, thank you.
- You're welcome.
Enjoy your war pizza!
The pizza hadn't even
cooled before Rebel arrived.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Oh, so this is a dorm.
This is a dorm.
Well, I suppose anything goes in a dorm.
You got that right.
Although, we should probably go inside,
because they don't like us
hanging out in the hallways, actually.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
George Michael had just
officially gotten over Maeby.
Thanks for, uh, keeping it down for my R.A.
You were keeping it down, right?
You know what really
impresses me about you?
How little you try to impress me.
Well, I aim to not please. (chuckles)
I just came from a dinner
with this right-wing politician
and his date, who was an actual hooker.
Oh, my God, they sound
like terrible people.
- Oh, they were.
- Huh.
So, wait, is this where
you conceived Fakeblock?
It was George Michael's first chance
to truly be unpretentious
and undo the big lie.
On the other hand, she thought
he was an unpretentious software genius.
If she were to learn that he
was merely a wood block player
with a heightened ability
to track the passage of time,
perhaps she would rightly feel
lack of pretention should be a given.
It was after second 23 that he said...
24. Yes, it was, uh, right in here.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
This is like making love
with the Wright brothers
in their bicycle shop.
I'm sure she just meant one of them.
Hey, how about her knowing
they had a bicycle shop?
Just a little token...
The next morning, he walked her to her car.
(sighs) Listen, I got to go shoot a PSA.
I'll text you from the car.
Oh, no, don't... don't do...
- Action.
- Tweet and drive.
Yeah, that was good, but it's "text."
And we need the word "don't."
And upon returning to his dorm,
he discovered that P-Hound had
officially filed a grievance
with the student housing office.
DOUG: So P-Hound claims
that George Michael...
Make a note of that; that's one person.
Oh, I know, I know.
Messed with his stuff
and stole some software thing?
Yeah, and, uh, George Michael claims
that nobody can live with P-Hound.
Somebody's got to go.
O... okay, it's time for a vote.
We'll each get one vote.
Oh, well, that doesn't really seem fair,
because you guys are obviously
gonna vote for the same person.
Oh, right, yeah, 'cause, uh, we're twins,
and, uh, we have no sense
of ourselves as individuals.
That's right.
BOTH: Fine.
We'll each get a half vote.
And the four men cast their three votes.
DOUG: It's a tie.
Uh, one and a half to one and a half.
The twins were proud to show that they
voted differently from one another.
Eh, we're gonna need a tiebreaker, ugly.
Fortunately, they were able to bring in
two more half voters...
- It's a tie. Two to two.
- ... who also proved
they were capable of
having opposite opinions.
Double tie!
- Yeah! Whoo!
To break the tie, more members of twin club
joined the electorate...
a quadruple tie!
Which also jammed up the works.
- Yeah!
- Yeah! Go, yeah.
Maybe we should just bring
in a single person now.
Uh, you mean like n... not a twin?
Yeah, just to speed things along a little.
And perhaps it was that comment...
I guess one head's better
than two, huh? Twin hater.
We've been dealing with
"twincists" like you
all our lives.
That united the voting body
into a greater cause than
expressing their individuality.
And with the exception
of George Michael's vote...
P-Hound.
George Michael. George
Michael. George Michael.
George Michael. George Michael.
- ... and one other curiosity...
- George Michael.
Bender fromFuturama.
- I almost wrote that.
- (Laughs)
it was a George Michael blitz.
DOUG: (sighs) George Michael and...
oh, a half vote for "George
Michael the twincist."
See you later, twin hater.
- No, I'm not...
- Uh, uh.
(whispers): Shh. Go.
And now wishing he'd
actually packed the bag
- I...
- OTHERS: Shh.
- George Michael aimlessly
headed out onto the campus
where, as fate would have it,
- (horn honks) Oh!
- He ran into his beeping uncle.
(bleep) What are you doing here?
I was in the neighborhood.
I happened to remember
how much you love bologna.
- Huh?
- So, yeah, I just... I found this great shop-rite
and I just thought, you
know who's got to have
a taste of this, is young George Michael.
He didn't think George
Michael liked bologna.
I know how you love bologna.
He was trying to correct
a bad impression he felt
he might have made with his
nephew a few nights earlier.
We're good.
My God, Uncle Gob, what is this?
Can't lie to you, George Michael,
it's a forget-me-now.
I wanted you to forget what happened
at that magic club; I was embarrassed.
If you don't want me to tell
anyone about it, I won't.
I'm such a fool.
I go to those things too quickly.
Really, it's just the
age we live in, isn't it?
Take a pill to forget your problems.
Take a pill to go to sleep.
And take a pill to forget your problems.
Need an erection, take a pill.
Need to forget your problems, take a pill.
Take a pill and your
problems are forgotten.
Just take a pill.
What an age we live in.
It's great, isn't it? (laughs)
What's with the suitcase?
I got kicked out of my dorm.
That was a freebie.
You in the market to buy a house?
It's a great time to buy.
Oh, I don't want to buy a house.
- I don't have that kind of money.
- Money?
(chuckles): Ninja please.
You don't need money.
With that Fakeblock thing you got going
and your great credit rating,
we can put you in a Bluth in no time.
Frankly, it wasn't the kind of risk
George Michael would take.
But then Gob said something
that changed his mind.
Plus, it would make your dad proud.
I know that he's still
really disappointed about
you, uh...
What, that I blew him off?
Blew him off.
Boy, is he disappointed about that.
I would love to say yes...
Yes! There it is!
I got my much vaunted yes!
Gob felt good.
He would be able to prove
to his brother that he
could actually sell a house.
George Michael felt good
because he could prove
to his father that he
did indeed support him.
And the residents of
Sudden Valley felt good,
because it turns out,
the very young-looking man
- who drove down their street
- Hi.
- That afternoon...
- Oh, hello, young man.
- Hi.
How young are you?
I'm good. How you doing?
No, how young are you?
Oh, I... I'm 22. 22 years...
- ... was over 21,
- 22? You look 16.
And they wouldn't have to search
for a home that was even more remote.
He's 22! He's 22, but looks 16.
- (doorbell rings)
- NARRATOR: Sudden Valley residents
wasted no time in welcoming George Michael
- Just wanted to welcome you
- To the community
- to the neighborhood.
- Every chance they got.
Thank you. Uh... Hi.
Hello again. Welcome back.
Hi. Hi.
Oh, it's so nice. Wow.
Like it's my birthday.
It's like it's everyone's birthday.
Oh, this is...
(chuckles) I wonder who this is from.
- We said no clothes, Carlos.
- Hat is not clothes.
- A hat is clothes.
- Gosh, I wish
I had something to offer you guys.
You know, here you are, guests in my home,
and you've gotten me these beautiful gifts.
You know, feels like it
should be the other way around.
(laughter)
MAN: Football!
Hut, hut.
- (Carlos laughs)
- Carlos...
Carlos, you're on my team.
You're on my team.
The play is dead. The play is dead.
The ball touched the ground.
Come on. The play is dead.
Carlos, man, we're on the same team.
Guys, maybe-maybe we can't
play skins versus skins.
Tops versus bottoms?
I got to bring my girlfriend up here.
- She's gonna love it.
- Let's throw her a party,
Sudden Valley style.
That actually sounds... Yeah, fun.
And so George Michael
was proud to invite Rebel
to see how successful
George Maharis had become
and how many people were
eager to be in his company.
No, I'm fine, I'm fine. He
was tickling me in there.
- Hey, um, what... what is all this?
- Hey. Just a little surprise.
- You did this for me?
- Yes.
- But Rebel had
- other concerns.
- We need to talk.
ALL: Ooh.
This is it.
This is the place.
Hope you don't find it too pretentious.
Well, what happened to the
old anything goes in the dorm?
Well, I got this place instead.
You know, I guess I wanted to impress you.
I'm gonna get some furniture, obviously.
- Right.
- The guys from home
fill are coming this week.
That's not the problem.
- No, that's not the problem.
- (Door opens)
Wrong house, buddy.
No, this is my son,
Lem Depardieu.
- Hey, baby.
- Hi.
Jacqueline still in the car?
(exhales) Oh, you have a son?
Yeah.
- Hey, Lem. How you doing?
- Hi.
I love kids. I'm great...
You want a Twister?
I was just given, like, four Twisters.
- You should take one.
- Wow.
- Go on, take a Twister.
- Oh. You know what, honey?
Do you want to give Mommy some
alone time with her friend?
Maybe he could go play in the pool.
- Yeah.
- He'll be totally safe.
There's like 100 guys out there.
- Yay!
- Make sure you wear your sunblock.
In fact, it was the folks
in the pool who were more at risk
of being near Lem than he was of them.
And perhaps that's what led Gob
to having to take out another ad.
GEORGE MICHAEL: Wow, what a great kid.
You know, when I said I was
not eager to have kids,
but I think it's great that you have a son.
You know, I have a spare room here
that the two of you could stay in.
Or maybe you could just stay in it.
He doesn't live with me.
He lives in France with his father.
He just visits March and April
during French pilot season,
but that's what I'm talking about.
I just don't want to get that serious.
Because you're seeing someone else?
No. I mean, yes.
I'm seeing someone else, but I don't want
to get serious with him, either,
and you're out telling people
in the neighborhood
that we're seeing each other.
What happened to the guy
who founded Fakeblock?
The guy who keeps things anonymous?
I can do anonymous.
You know, I'm all about staying anonymous.
That's Fakeblock's mission statement.
And then you're asking Lem
and me to move into this house,
and it just, it seems all backwards.
(sighs)
Sorry.
(door closes)
Maybe it is backwards.
George Michael shared
his relationship problem
with the one other woman
he'd had a relationship problem with.
GEORGE MICHAEL: Well, she's
not really my girlfriend.
I mean, I'm crazy about her,
but she wants to keep things anonymous,
- and I don't know how to do that.
- Oh, that's ridiculous.
- Right.
- You haven't told her
your real name yet, have you?
What? No, no.
No, she still thinks I'm George Maharis,
but she's dating another
guy, which is probably
the whole reason she's always
saying I'm moving too fast.
I take things too seriously.
I take things too serious.
I need to note which
one of those is correct,
because I sound like a horse's ass
when I alternate between the two of them.
I need to get my (bleep) together.
- Yeah.
- But the point is that I take things
easily-breezily.
Well, a real "serioush" woman
knows what she wants and moves quickly.
"Serioush" is nothing. That's not a word.
Are you ready to see your office?
I have been; it's great.
I like it a lot. It...
I wonder if she's gonna think
we've been a little lavish with money.
You know, is it too much?
But then to contradict myself,
I do think at some point,
it would be good to get a second chair
just in case we have a guest,
but I'm thinking big picture.
Of course, that wasn't his office.
This isn't your office.
She's over here.
And it was at his actual desk
where he made his first
major decision as CEO.
- Maeby, you're fired!
- (Tires screech)
And although Mort was prepared
to be handed his walking papers,
there was nothing that could
have prepared George Michael
for what Mort would leave on his desk.
And so, later that day, Hey. Hey.
It was a disgruntled Maeby
that ran into Michael-Hey.
As he was seeking a
signature for his movie.
I think movies are dead.
Maybe it's a TV show.
What? No. This girl that I'm dating, Rebel,
she's gonna be in it,
and she would never do TV.
You're dating Rebel Alley?
Yeah. I have a picture of us
to prove it; I can't find it,
- but yeah.
- So...
you're the other guy.
You know her personally?
Yes. I mean,
that's how I know that you were dating her.
Do you know the other
guy that she's dating?
And that's when she saw an opportunity
to get back at George Michael.
No, no, but, um,
I know it's over.
She is dumping him.
She dumping him?
Apparently, he was coming on too strong,
taking it too seriously.
She hates that.
- Is that what she said?
- Yeah,
that's what she told me.
Just kills it for her.
She wants it easily-breezily.
Well, that's... informative.
I owe you. Thank you.
No, you don't.
Okay, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait.
Don't knock, just...
- Okay.
- One second.
Mm-hmm.
And so fortified
with Maeby's information that Rebel
- was breaking up with her other beau...
- Hello.
- Michael.
- Michael decided
- to move things along.
- I want you
to know that I think that
I've been coming on a
little bit too strong.
I got a lot going on; I got the movie.
You know, a bunch of stuff
with the housing complex, and I'm just...
I'm not gonna be pressuring you anymore.
I want to just keep it easy-peasy.
- Yeah.
- Cool, totally.
- Keep it loose.
- Yeah.
And we'll have some fun with, you know...
If the fun, you know...
Someday, one day, it gets more serious,
you know, then, uh, then it does,
and we, uh,
we're walking down the
aisle, you know, and...
I'm saying it wrong, saying
it wrong, 'cause I get,
uh, I get tongue-tied, um...
uh, because I think that you
are coming on too strong.
- You know? Bugging me.
- Oh, uh,
you want to come in?
No.
- Ooh.
- Yeah? Yeah.
It was the best sex Michael had ever had.
REBEL (sighs): That was great.
Was that fun for you?
No.
(chuckles)
Are you gonna take a photo of me?
Uh, no.
No, no, I've been trying to get a signal.
But he did want a picture of them together,
which I why he grabbed the one
he saw from the photo booth.
Are you gonna call me?
If I'm in traffic.
Although he was growing concerned
about how he was going to keep this up.
Hey.
♪ I just stole this fair young miss ♪
♪ From a big shot, George Mahar... ♪
(bleep)
NARRATOR: Michael had just found out
- (phone line ringing)
- That the woman he loved
was also dating his son.
- (phone rings)
- So, after placing a call
- to the niece who sent him there...
- Hello?
You're out of the movie.
(paper ripping, horn honking over phone)
and at an emotional impasse,
he decided it was time
to deal with Gob
and the Sudden Valley problem.
(scoffs) Pervert.
Excuse me?
And that's when Michael
ran into a son-Dad, hey.
George Michael, what are you doing here?
Who was eager to make him proud.
I... I'm home.
But George Michael had
suddenly found himself
- with enormous debt
- You bought this house?
- And tried to hide his panic.
- Why would you buy
one of these pieces of sh...
short-term investments?
Well, you know, Gob told me that you wanted
to start selling these
things, not just renting them,
and I knew it was important to you.
He said all that, huh? Oh, boy, that was...
That's... nice of him.
How... how could you afford
one of these houses, buddy.
Well, I have a lot of money coming in
- from investors for my software thing...
- Okay.
And I don't know what's gonna
happen with that, so I thought
I'd do what everyone around
here says: put it into Bluth.
- Yeah, who else is saying that?
- You know, it's an expression.
- Neighbors.
- I don't like it.
- Can I offer you anything?
- No.
I just got two more boxes
of Twister from the neighbors.
- Oh, boy, return them.
- Feel like I have one
for every day of the week now.
Anyway, you know, I figure that
worse case scenario is I
sell this place, and I get
my money back. It's not like
- they're going down in value, right?
- Well...
It's a great community.
- Nobody locks their doors around here.
- You should.
Plus, I... I wanted to make it up to you.
You know, I felt terrible
about what happened with the dorm and...
- Wow.
- And things between us.
And I... I've screwed up a lot of things
in the past few weeks,
and, you know, this is the one thing
that I know I did right.
I mean, who would not want
to raise their kids here?
And perhaps this is why he
didn't give him the bad news
about the neighborhood.
Thank you.
Thanks, but you didn't
need to do it for me, pal.
Now he just needed to get
out of the house before...
You know, to be totally honest,
I didn't just do it for you.
- Yeah?
- I also did it for my girlfriend.
Kind of wanted to impress her.
That came up.
Wow.
You got a girlfriend.
Good for you. That's great.
Congratulations.
Your dad's got one, too.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yep.
How is yours going?
Not great.
I haven't been completely honest with her
about who I am.
You know, I haven't even
told her my real name,
and I don't think
I can keep that lie going, so...
I think it might be over.
(sighing): Oh, great...
pain fades slowly.
Quickly.
- But now it was as simple as getting out...
- Thanks.
- Before George Michael asked...
- But what about you?
You're doing great, huh?
Tell me about your girlfriend,
and you're producing this movie now.
That.
I think they're both over.
Yeah, it wasn't meant to be.
I'm sorry.
And that's when Michael finally
treated his son like an adult.
Hey, you know what I miss on you?
The mustache.
And so, discouraged, Michael returned
to his apartment, only to find worse news.
And when he saw that Lucille 2
was having a campaign event at Cinco,
he knew there was only
one thing he could give her
instead of the money.
And he knew what he had to do first
to give it to her.
George Michael, meanwhile,
had a keynote speech to give,
and hadn't totally decided
whether he should come clean.
And that's when he ran into his uncle.
We'll take care of.
My father's got the money.
- You guys are one heck of a horde.
- Uncle Gob!
- No, you're mistaken, friend.
- No, it's George Michael.
- Hi. Exactly.
- Yes.
Hey, I'm actually really
glad I ran into you.
I could use some advice.
Oh. Love each other.
Oh, no, that's great, but I actually need
a specific piece of advice
for a certain situation.
I'll give it to you fast.
Basically, for the past few
weeks, I've been living a lie.
I've been... in this
relationship with a woman
who doesn't even know.
- It's probably over with the girl.
- * *
♪ ♪
- ... gone way too far...
So, basically now I can either tell her...
♪ ♪
That there is no George Maharis
and never was... or...
we keep things anonymous
and I continue the lie
that Fakeblock exists.
From my perspective...
something about "there's a girl... "
Did you... Does she like you?
I mean, you're not the
world's most handsome guy.
Yeah, no, she likes...
I would say what I did take away was that
I would rather have sex with someone
because they thought I was someone else
than not have sex with someone
because they thought I was me.
So I should probably do
the opposite of that and...
be true to who I am and
not compromise my integrity
just for some fleeting sexual experience.
- So, "love each other."
- There it is.
It wasn't much help,
and as George Michael headed off
unsure of what to do, Gob
went off to find his father,
who was having his own relationship crisis.
We're getting a real divorce.
You're out of the marriage.
So I am fat.
GOB: Boy, am I glad you're here.
I need money and it's
not for what you think...
for a magic show or a bee colony...
it's to pay the builders I hired
to start building the fake wall
between Mexico and America.
Shh! Are you crazy?
Lucille 2 is around here.
Well, don't worry about Lucille 2.
I'll handle her.
It's just that I need to pay the Chinese.
Wait, wait, you... you hired Chinese?!
Well, I figured who better than
the Chinese to build a wall.
(George Sr. stammers)
But, no, I couldn't afford them,
so I... I hired, um, they're
technically Mongols, I guess.
They're, well, they're the
people that they built the wall
to try to keep out...
How many did you hire?
A horde. That's the minimum.
They don't come in
anything less than a horde.
So you hired a Mongol horde.
Look, Dad, just, if they
don't get their money soon,
they're gonna be really mad
and then they're gonna have
a major Mongolian beef
with us... there they are.
Okay, uh, we don't have any m... money.
Well, he says that we don't have any money.
♪ ♪
And at that moment, another
Bluth who had no money
was finding a way to pay up.
What are you doing?
I'm gonna have sex with you.
For money.
Oh!
- Oh, I didn't realize
- Yeah.
How heavy these rings are.
- But I thought you were gonna kiss me
and I panicked.
I... I was gonna kiss you.
I didn't even try to do it that time.
So, it's, uh, let's take a tumble
with Old Moneybags, right?
And she'll be so grateful that
she'll walk away from $700,000.
No, no, no, it would
absolutely not be a gift.
This would still be a loan, okay?
However, my lovemaking
would be, you know...
What?
What, Michael? What were you gonna say?
Something that I would never
be able to take back, but...
I didn't want that to happen.
Now, listen, you have been the one
that has been flirting with me.
- Those were pity flirts.
- No, they were not.
You want this as much as I do.
As much as I want this extension.
Two different "this" es.
Now, you own a company
that I helped to build.
It was all of my hard work.
This is something you have
to do because, if you don't,
I can't be held responsible
for what I might do.
As it turns out,
George Michael was the only Bluth
who could be responsible for what he did,
and as he headed to the microphone,
Mongols, not paid what they were promised,
did what they do best.
Um... Oh! Ah!
Viva Méjico.
Which lead to this.
(chanting): Put up this wall!
And it's hard to know
whether it was the chanting
- of "Put up this wall... "
- Ladies and gentlemen,
if I could have your
attention for a moment...
or the note that promised
him a sexual resumption
of his anonymous relationship with Rebel...
that made him say this:
Yeah, so, I'm George Maharis, and, uh...
and Fakeblock is real...
(crowd cheering, whooping)
- Let's put up this wall.
- (Chanting): Put up this wall!
But not everyone wants to
put up a wall on the Internet.
Let's put up, put up this
wall. Have a good night.
And the Anonymous who
left the note wasn't Rebel.
A discouraged Michael
returned to the model home,
where he ran into a brother
who also had something to hide.
As an emboldened George
Maharis gave Rebel a note
that she now believed he'd written for her.
And for the son, it
was a night to remember,
and for the father, a night to forget.
- * So easy to forget. *
- Shh.
- NARRATOR: It was May 5,
- MICHAEL: Rebel, it's Michael.
And while Rebel was on the phone,
George Michael was realizing
that taking things casually
was not going to be an option for him.
You can come over later, okay?
- Good-bye.
- MICHAEL: I'll see you soon.
Who was that?
No one.
Look, I... I don't care.
I... I don't care that
you're seeing someone else.
I... I just, I want to continue this.
I'm ready to try and make this work.
I'll fight anyone I have to for you.
I'm not going to pretend
I don't care about you.
I'm a grown-up man and...
I want to get serious.
Wow. Serious.
Things are getting serious.
And the girl who was never capable
of making a commitment...
Okay.
Suddenly found herself making too many.
George Michael felt good.
And, at least for that day,
he wouldn't encounter his
father in Rebel's bedroom...
He'd run into him leaving the building.
(laughs): Hey.
What are you doing here?
I'm vi... I'm on a visit.
I'm visiting.
My girlfriend lives here... Rebel.
Wow. So you're gonna work
it out with your girlfriend.
Good for you. That's great news.
- Great to see you again.
- That says "Rebel," huh?
Is that a... is that
a little gift for Rebel?
I'm dating Rebel Alley.
So there better be two
Rebels in here, am I right?
I'm dating Rebel Alley.
(both laugh)
That'd be weird.
No, ironically, she did say
that there was another guy,
but that his name was George...
- ... Maharis.
- Maharis. That's me.
You're George Michael.
No, but, uh, yeah, but I
use the name George Maharis
when... with women, because
I hate the name George Michael.
I told you that.
This is, uh, this is weird.
Are you not kidding me?
It's insane... no...
so, you're the other guy.
I'm the oth... well, you're the other guy.
Yeah, well, one of us.
Did I not tell you that we were alike?
Exactly alike.
- This is just...
- So horrifying.
Too funny.
This is what I was talking about.
I told you.
I mean, we're like twins.
Are we not like twins?
All the way down to the photo booth.
You name me one way in
which we're different.
Well, Dad, you know, I
never, in a million years,
would have gone out
with her, if I knew that
you were, you know, the other guy.
Me, neither.
I wouldn't have, either.
Damn it. You know?
You gotta believe me.
This is just...
- This is, uh...
- Yeah...
How'd you know about the photo booth?
How... you... 'cause you said,
"Right down to the photo... "
I said, "Right down to the photo booth."
Ironically, he could've
told the truth and said
he'd taken a forget-me-now.
But like the victim of a roofie circle,
having taken one was the
only memory he had lost.
So, instead, he doubled-down on this.
It's like we're identical twi...
♪ ♪
- (ringtone playing)
- Gob gets an important call
- from his mother.
- Hello.
- LUCILLE: She's gone.
Lucille 2 has disappeared and
it's time for you to step up
and be president of the Bluth Company.
Keep your nose clean. No scandals!
Okay.
And even though Gob hadn't
taken a forget-me-now
- the night before...
- (Phone rings)
it seems Tony Wonder had.
TONY: Hey, Gobie. It's Tony.
We still on for our sex date tonight?
- (knocking)
- And this happens...
Oh! Okay.
Are you Buster Bluth?
I am.
- Okay, this...
- Can we come in?
This isn't my house.
- What is this regarding?
- That's all right.
You're under arrest for the
murder of Lucille Austero.
Read him his rights.
Okay, I think there's
been some kind of mistake.
That left hand might be difficult to cuff.
- Trouble cuffing him.
- I'm not a monster!
- (handcuff clicks)
- I got it.
Uh... all right, great.
(Buster whimpering)
Well, the infamous Bluth
family is at it again,
this time facing murder charges,
and our Imagine cameras
were there to capture it all.
Hey, did you see this?
Yeah, I saw it just now in the elevator.
Is this the family
you've been talking about?
It sure is.
Wow! You got the rights to this?
Well, only for the
killer... but that's enough
for us to get a green light, right?
Absolutely! It's our nextDa Vinci Code!
Yay! That's great!
Plus, it's gonna put
Imagine News on the map.
This is John Beard.
Remember: Love each other.